// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which component is used to compile, debug and execute the java programs?",
    answer: "JDK",
    options: [
      "JRE",
      "JIT",
      "JDK",
      "JVM"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one of the following is not a Java feature?",
    answer: "Use of pointers",
    options: [
      "Object-oriented",
      "Use of pointers",
      "Portable",
      "Dynamic and Extensible"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is a type of polymorphism in Java Programming?",
    answer: "Compile time polymorphism",
    options: [
      "Multiple polymorphism",
      "Compile time polymorphism",
      "Multilevel polymorphism",
      "Execution time polymorphism"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the extension of compiled java classes?",
    answer: ".class",
    options: [
      ".txt",
      ".js",
      ".class",
      ".java"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which exception is thrown when java is out of memory?",
    answer: "OutOfMemoryError",
    options: [
      "MemoryError",
      "OutOfMemoryError",
      "MemoryOutOfBoundsException",
      "MemoryFullException"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of these packages contains the exception Stack Overflow in Java?",
    answer: "java.lang",
    options: [
      "java.io",
      "java.system",
      "java.lang",
      "java.util"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of these keywords are used for the block to be examined for exceptions?",
    answer: "try",
    options: [
      "check",
      "throw",
      "catch",
      "try"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which one of the following is not an access modifier?",
    answer: "Void",
    options: [
      "Protected",
      "Void",
      "Public",
      "Private"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the below is not a Java Profiler?",
    answer: "JVM",
    options: [
      "JProfiler",
      "Eclipse Profiler",
      "JVM",
      "JConsole"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is a superclass of every class in Java?",
    answer: "Object class",
    options: [
      "ArrayList",
      "Abstract class",
      "Object class",
      "String"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];